<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on An Do</title>
    <link>https://andoDsAI.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on An Do</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 14:50:51 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://andoDsAI.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT Prompts</title>
      <link>https://andoDsAI.github.io/p/chatgpt-prompts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 14:50:51 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andoDsAI.github.io/p/chatgpt-prompts/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to the &amp;ldquo;ChatGPT Prompts&amp;rdquo;! This is a collection of prompt examples to be used with the ChatGPT model.
The ChatGPT model is a large language model trained by OpenAI that is capable of generating human-like text. By providing it with a prompt, it can generate responses that continue the conversation or expand on the given prompt.
What is the prompt in ChatGPT? ChatGPT Prompts The &amp;ldquo;prompts&amp;rdquo; in ChatGPT refers to a sentence or a passage of text provided by the user to initiate a conversation with the system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cà phê thế nào là ngon?</title>
      <link>https://andoDsAI.github.io/p/ca-phe-the-nao-la-ngon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 19:10:13 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andoDsAI.github.io/p/ca-phe-the-nao-la-ngon/</guid>
      <description>Một số bài viết nếu được viết bằng tiếng Việt sẽ thể hiện rõ được cảm xúc cũng như ý kiến của mình hơn (thật ra là do tiếng Anh của mình kém :&amp;gt;). Vì vậy, một số bài viết mình xin phép được viết bằng tiếng Việt, ví dụ như bài viết này.
Chắc hẳn nhiều anh em cũng như mình, cà phê không chỉ là đồ uống, cà phê trở thành một phần không thể thiếu trong cuộc sống thường ngày.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make a Github Blog</title>
      <link>https://andoDsAI.github.io/p/how-to-make-a-github-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andoDsAI.github.io/p/how-to-make-a-github-blog/</guid>
      <description>Hi, this is my way to make a Github blog for my self, which will contain blogs, some projects, and some tips from my experience. I am a website newbie, so it took me almost 2 days to setup from start to finish, and it&amp;rsquo;s pretty easy. Here is how I made it.
Initial setup Create repositories First, let take a look at what a Github Page is, and how to create one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What this blog is all about?</title>
      <link>https://andoDsAI.github.io/p/what-this-blog-is-all-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 14:50:51 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://andoDsAI.github.io/p/what-this-blog-is-all-about/</guid>
      <description>Some first words Sweet, my blog, is a storybook of mine that is about all aspects of my life, and knowledge I learned in a life of living (I’m not sure about that, my life is quite boring). I am a data scientist. I am excited to share my experiences and insights with you about data science, artificial intelligence, and other topics that interest me.
Why did I name my site “Sweet”?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
